oh no sorry ass obvious is the streamer
or software on yeah I don't think so I
mean I think we might have been lied
that one time
can you chat my chat room Oh live POG Oh
Lucas oh you can hear me right now yeah
it's like broken I don't know
oh wait what a five oh it's working out
high five yours yeah sweet Lucas can
hear me alright
did you get a note no they probably
didn't that's why I'm only a 5 your and
your your like you have notifications on
usually alright we got people now oh
okay this man is insane big fan from
Bangladesh let's go yo I'm glad why am i
outside what oh yeah don't share balls
[Laughter]
Unreal 4 engine looks good what's up
hello hot outside yet no well I don't
have a mask on and you know listen to my
soundcloud if you have any questions
dude you can't go outside well you know
what I don't know what anti-freedom
place you live in but this is America oh
yeah you show them a hundred ninety-two
alright show them you yeah hello I'm
here with Alex
you all remember Alex this is wonderful
how outside has nice graphics dude I
know
hey guys I got wild rendering so it's
not gonna be a long stream today zoom
back this is the protein sort of folded
and we'll get back to that in another
stream but um no Alex and I were just
talking about predictions for the future
it's true yeah so we thought we'd share
them with you have you read the papers
Kelly released the paper I saw Danny
yeah is it good huh but you didn't see
his plea I lead you to it
Oh she'll let him out of jail for
coronavirus but I
Alex I thought this was just another
scam I thought this was like the Hillary
Clinton hair thing they should have let
him out a long time ago but that time
you defrauded people and made them all
money see no futurism is coming the
resolution is insane you mean it's good
you mean all right I would get any
predictions all right so we started
today's conversation about decades have
passed maybe we started with the
observation that everybody thinks
culture is declining and shitty that's
the past there's a moan in the past that
where things were perfect ingredient so
from my perspective you know everything
in the 90s was perfect and great the 90s
the 90s was the I don't know I wasn't
alive for the eighteen nineties but all
I know is that like like kids are
playing pokemons go today well ship him
we invented Pokemon in the 90s wasn't me
but you know um so
guys I'm not that worried about the
social distancing only from old people
if you were 30 and you catch coronavirus
you're probably gonna be where people
over 100 have died then under 30 yeah
that's just something that puts this
stuff in perspective um but yeah all
right so well no we talked remember how
we through the 30 years thing okay the
60s man well yeah yeah you can't argue
that a decade that ended with the
greatest human accomplishment ever
putting people on the moon was a decline
no no certainly not just like a brief
like the 60s was clearly an ascent right
right um so we talked about the Internet
the internet between 20 during 2000 to
2010 you gained all these awesome new
powers and I argue that the Internet's
gotten worse in the last ten years do
great you're on my podcast Heyward
debating really when it started
happening 2010 2020 clean well was
thrown out yeah when I worked at
Facebook I think that was 2012 not agree
you don't think so I don't agree it
became everything we had yeah yeah I
think there's no like if you compare
Google Maps from 2000 to 2010 huge
changes if you compare Google Maps in
2010 to 2020 they're the same if you
compare video games from 2000 to 2010
you know quantum leap forward right we
went from like like halo 1 to modern
warfare 7 yeah and now we're on modern
warfare 14 that looks just like modern
warfare 7
not internet bad but big companies that
are bad well yeah I mean I think in a
way that that kind of over simplifies it
but it is these companies that have they
stopped trying to make a better services
and they've just tried to extract more
value
well first off because people have have
had it with how do you know like think
about how much you know anti e-tec
backlash there was in 2010 versus
anti-tech backlash from 2020 sure yeah
you know Joe Biden is clearly going to
be a phenomenally strong leader and
guide us through this Joe Biden's gonna
lose Joe Rogan say he vote for like a
man-eating plant over Joe Biden who was
Alex do you want to introduce yourself
no just you can make something up
[Music]
Alex was raised on a boat it's from the
ages of 1 to 16 with 16 other people
yeah but she got out she's pretty normal
now government checks Joe exotic for
president yo I mean if you pulled that
off right now could he pardon himself
Carol Baskin assassinated by Drew we're
in Golden Gate Park
yeah the quarantine is a little
overhyped guys yeah I wouldn't you know
go to a bar or Club but you know I
wouldn't go to a club I wouldn't go I
don't go to the club
well that's true I mean you know
that was that was that was China circa
2010 back in the world was so good you
love Clark the free plate absolutely
those dragon fruits yeah those were good
enough occasionally they'd bring out
like duck liver or something and be like
damn
terrible food and then one time they
brought out bat no just kidding they
don't eat bats in China so by the virus
escaped from a lab but we're doing
projections yeah yeah we're doing
prediction in Manhattan you're locked up
here I mean are you what does the law
actually say you can look into that you
guys know any cities where things are
still happening I'll get on a plane
we'll go there yeah we could go to a
rest in the UK you get a $50 fine in the
UK you also get a $50 fine for like
saying something about Muslims on
Twitter so you know I don't know about
you guys and then on a free speech you
guys fight for free speech free speech
is important free speech is one of my
favorite things about America yes Sweden
isn't sweetener that closed down I think
they closed the border about
I mean Iceland is not closed down either
no they won't let me into Sweden and as
they shouldn't I'm from the I'm from the
country with more coronavirus than
anywhere why would they let me into
Sweden I mean I think you might be able
to go to Taiwan but you have to do a
government mandate of 14 North Korea is
operating normally
all the propaganda from North Korea says
they're operating normally
thoughts on Carmack leaving oculus and
focusing on AGI I've actually spoken
with Carmack recently we did talk we
think talk to Carmack about this I'm
very uh I you know I'm always optimistic
I'm cautiously optimistic I think the
man is a genius and I think he has some
interesting ideas that are at least
worth trying yeah
they banned the virus
[Laughter]
okay make predictions on AGI so I'm
definitely bearish on AGI by on anything
that would be considered AGI by 2030 but
okay so we started out with I think that
we are either going to have people on
Mars or be very close all the combat
that's why we kept that's not ours to
share who is that I was involved as
reminder ship but um so and this isn't
gonna be like the time we went to the
moon and we sent like three people there
and then we went back because that was
done by the government just to you know
wave their dick at the Russians the moon
landing was actually faked that would
that would seriously that would
seriously make me undermine my ability
to think about anything
[Laughter]
alex is not in biz dev don't worry
computer computer is gonna do it okay so
another prediction um
the Star Trek Universal Translator will
I mean I think it's gonna take time for
it to actually be good but basically
yeah because yeah it's not gonna be like
we already have the underlying tech for
you know there's always this problem of
how do you block out their voice noise
cancelling headphones bro we're still
put on yeah put on some air pod sevens
and you can hear the whole world in
English
already goes in your ear and does some
amount of time it's probably like Google
glass and tariffs oh I don't know
predictions on the rise of cam girls
post Kovac I mean I think camp girls
it's a golden era it is it is a golden
era of cam girls easy if you'd like to
get somebody to base themselves online
for you prices have never been lower
that's like the oil markets right now
dropped for cowgirls I don't know I mean
you don't really have prices they kind
of operate on a donation model a lot of
them so if there were an actual
efficient market yes prices would have
drops yeah everyone's live right now uh
yeah you might start an only fans all
only fans is really you want to start
not like that no no no that was some
subscriber who said it that's why I read
it because subscribers are better people
than nonsubscribers pro tip to you other
people we don't stream for free bros
it's true it's true karma doesn't pay me
anymore six feet apart oh no no we
protest we stand we fight the authority
you're not even giving them your best
prediction well okay we're we're so so
yeah so that's it we went thank you for
subscribing who subscribed em bmz all
big girls one big Griz
what's the chest move against dropping
the CEO veg bro there's no chest move I
just didn't like being CEO suck
then I realized that I had jump is gonna
win if Trump doesn't win twenty to
twenty but I think I mean I predict that
the only way the coronavirus will affect
Trump's re-election is if he gets it in
guys paper Martinelli releases the
coronavirus oh no oh yeah we know I'm
sure I'm sure Martin shkreli is off I
don't know George a 33 year old guy in
my area died somebody somebody's gonna
die right like statistically again this
isn't if this was a disease that a
hundred people had and a 33 year old
died in your area that's different this
is a disease that has half a million
confirmed cases in the US
oh come like sorry I was like covering
the mic oh I don't know um that's why I
have to hold it like this we really need
honey booboo for president no I mean I
think at the end of the decade all the
candidates are gonna be I mean we need
to have some kind of or okay fine you
know you can also I will say that all of
my predictions are in the optimistic
camp I mean we could do we could do
pessimistic twenty productions all the
candidates in 2030 look like Joe Biden
[Music]
predictions on streaming video quality
improving now I'm not I'm not a
pessimist I genuinely have very high
hopes for this for this decade
no no military's our economy no but uh
oh we'll Bitcoin moon no I'm very
bearish on I do watching it's gonna be a
little bit better but it's still gonna
remain a theory um's not gonna have like
they're gonna actually fix the capacity
issues like it is going to get better I
think there's no doubt that it's gonna
get better this like blockchain is going
to replace the money it's better yeah
like like easier to use of course well
it just isn't
um yeah sharding will happen show you
around beautiful San Diego not in San
Diego San Francisco
George listicle coins like tethered to
the alright we're rooting for our
prediction markets would be great
because then we could figure out you
know all of these models made by
government shells a prediction market is
gonna tell you exactly how many people
are gonna die of coronavirus yeah right
I mean if the prediction market really
gets big enough you can have people like
voting for something and then like you
know are influencing politics I lost
money every day
what you better I did not Biden oh you
got you went not Biden for oh I've only
bet one son predicted and it was on
Trump in 2016 and I made 16x returns on
that I don't even think I think I think
Trump is already bottomed out if you can
get there's a classic predictive meme in
the comments where it's like you know
people like fake shill fur there's no
way down is what I'm saying
I know so that so that they can buy
cheap Trump ships I mean there's tons of
discord some of them you could even pay
to be a member of where people tell me
where the Zoomers congregate
we wanted or the zoo we want to know if
new culture is happening and we're just
old isn't winning of Trump a good thing
I mean it depends who the opponent is
versus Joe Biden sorry I'm pulling the
same thing Joe Rogan said yes it's it's
like did Carol Baskin kill her husband
though I think no I don't and I think
that there's actually like if you look
online there's more to that story that
involves like the husband's yeah I mean
I think Carol Baskin killing her husband
is too convenient for the gel exotic
narrative almost
yeah yeah um karabast
don't get me wrong I thought she was
bitch
not every bitch what will happen with
snow tonight I mean oh my opinion of the
Apple Google partnership put it this way
if they don't actually give you a way to
opt out maybe I'll get back into
jailbreaking now I wouldn't go that far
but actually would switch on Android on
and I'd commented out if they if they
tried it if they try to push Public
Health into my phone without me you
know what I'm a nice guy I probably
opt-in the Apple Google maybe like you
know I think oh I don't know no this is
these are short-term predictions they're
not making short-term predictions on
this dream short-term predictions are
yeah we haven't we haven't been talking
about the mainstream topic really um so
I think that AI is going to get good
um and I will make the most common
related prediction I think in five years
we will have level 3 level 4 working I
think in 10 years we'll have level 5 um
so I think self-driving cars or
something that's definitely gonna happen
in the next decade I put my money on
before 20:37
the self-driving cars yeah oh I think
the 2030s are that are the real severity
yeah I think I think the light 2039 is a
singularity but I think the 2020s again
I mean in a way all of you here on this
stream oh you wanna see the windmill
[Music]
tech talent migrate - that's a good one
there the world ends in 2038 the world
you yeah it's gonna be y2k again yeah
the UNIX timestamp roll all over the new
white you came out wall is 64-bit
computers by then VR innovations yes so
I think that's gonna be yeah I think
that's gonna be a big is David's
prediction public yeah I think by the
end of the decade we're going to have
really good both VR and I think AR
technology will be in common use oh no I
think I think as phone replacements okay
no phone we have headsets I think you'll
have a place oh yeah I think I think
it's the iPods you know yeah I mean no
maybe not if we're walking together like
I don't think it'll be that I think it's
like together we do yeah and like
sometime I think it's like air pods all
right do we put on air pods together cuz
it is personal in the same way exactly I
think that's how often we'd have
headsets on but I see headsets being the
new air box phone that's gonna be a bit
of a technical challenge I think we're
gonna have high bandwidth streaming to
headsets before we have and what am I
gonna be watching you just born he's
like what's going on in my head what do
you mean everything you know yes you're
I'm walking around with it so I
can see
I think there's gonna be walking around
with it well I think our gonna be like
VRA our headsets and you'll be able to
dim the outside world and rise it up all
right in the same way you can no rise
and dim like the air pod noise
cancelling it off you're basically just
gonna get air pods for your eyes I am
rooting for Apple yeah close to the end
yeah which I mean okay my prediction is
let's say 2027 because about about lack
of new technology yeah what's the new
curve well there's no new curves really
it's just gonna be things are finally
gonna get good right what were the new
curves in the 60s the sixties will win
like nuclear power got good the nuclear
missiles got good like that's the end of
the nuclear curve oh yeah yeah we went
to atomic city in Idaho who's gonna win
with a RV our unity are unreal oh yeah
are we gonna walk on beaches
nuke war I don't think we're gonna have
a nuke war you the curve baby yeah we're
gonna do it
valve on VR that's not clear no one
wanted to yard yeah well AI impact on
education system well I'm very bearish
on anything today that we call education
[Music]
so okay full disclosure in the 2020s I'm
gonna take my comment a I earnings and
I'm gonna start a cult it's not a cult
it's a chair well you know one let's use
the word universe a school a school a
place of Education it's going to be free
for everybody who can get there and who
can pass an entrance test no yeah put
this way like if I'm thinking about it
aren't other people to Plato's Academy
fagor is did this right where do you
sign up there's no sign up yet we're
looking at properties you know again we
need a few more years of comma AI
winning self-driving cars full
disclosure my position on coronavirus is
somewhat influenced by the fact that I'm
a small business owner in America you
know one of those people creating jobs
for the middle class when's the next
kovat nineteen stream guys I did 25
hours of research live on stream another
25 off stream I'm over I'm over coded 19
I think there's only so much you can do
there's so much you can do right what
kind of new information you can glean
well let me give it some time the
question was like is this is this
something that's incredibly high risk to
me is this something that's medium risk
to me or is this something that's quite
low risk
my conclusion is it's quite low risk -
Trillian no oversight yeah I mean it's
just a scam well let's not get the gold
right
I don't not really one of those fringe
gold guys I like pretending to be a
fringe gold guy sometime no but um you
know there's a we saw some stickers
around here what was it boycott rent SF
yeah well so if your boycott rent who
are you ripping off right
fundamentally someone has to pay for all
of this and it's not gonna be the elites
because they're scammers it's not gonna
be the poor people because they don't
have any money right the last the last
40 years have been a great wealth
extraction from the American middle
class
you see it all the thing coming equality
and then who actually doesn't have the
power
oh you behind oh you have a viewer
following you behind maybe I think it's
all we care about dated fold it kind of
fold it and we'll get it out in the
bubble screen
thoughts on PS 5 it's the same
is the last one money printer Goldberg
yeah and yet we do have to do something
about that money printer I mean
personally I don't know actually Alex to
be completely honest I don't actually
know what the ramifications of gold
would be something no something I am
very much Pro is that like the Fed
internally should have you don't need a
blockchain you just need not is a
database yeah right like a database
that's auditable by anyone in the public
you can print money but you better let
us all know exactly how much money you
printed it's all insider training
very high-profile yeah now this is this
is normal this is normal they're they're
such scammers with that market the SEC
is not an organization designed to
protect you not letting you invest in
comma AI the SEC is an organization
designed to protect to institutional
Wall Street I mean those are most of
these I don't think I think this is the
same pattern in every one of our
governmental institutions yeah all right
like the same way Google became scammer
well the SEC became scammer the SEC is
founded to prevent poor people from
having access to investment because
they're too stupid to know the risk bro
have you been on Robin Hood have you
been on our wall street bets do I think
Ovid 19 will seriously change our
society
no I've hit it slow I'm not making any
stupid real-time predictions about the
stock market I'm continuously surprised
yeah I really should go so do I think
handshakes will come back no handshakes
are dead and we never liked handshakes
Trump was ahead of the curve with that
drop gets done in by the old coronavirus
thing round germophobe done in by germs
um I never liked a hand it's Bernie
Sanders got some bad news about Bernie
Sanders I hope you guys got your refund
I got my refund he's getting a refund I
didn't donate it but uh that's good wow
that's pretty nice of Bernie man what a
good guy we'll break the 35 percent THC
mark on weed yes I want it naturally
growing I don't know you can only buy
some of those pens
I took yeah I don't know I took a hit of
a weed pen once there's growing Tommy's
eighty-five percent THC Wow I look like
a small head I was five for the three
hours do you think there will be more
remote jobs I think we were slowly on a
trajectory towards remote but I do I
think mushrooms will be legal yes oh
yeah we're getting yeah I mean I think
we have to do something about all drugs
it was odd kind of no you really don't
what do they do they meet do they want
to try them like what most of them have
tried also you guys I've written things
that you're on drugs all time it's true
man it's true
I mean they said this is Gary well like
the Trump sauna had a roll Trump said
how things are all tricks on songs no we
should go watch old Tom videos see what
we think actually I think people confuse
Trump's inability to read with I've
never used the teleprompter it's true
did you ever post on wall street that's
not oh my god
my mom calls me asking her advice on the
stock market should we Sal should we
tell now what do you say I say Holly not
buckets generally go up trumps aunt
modafinil
it's weird
so we're drunk not obvious how it feels
or what it does my dad was a drug I've
tried it's low-key good new go pill on
go pill for like the military well I
think they fed me now I mean they could
give people in it well you know I mean
you know about the trajectory of
antidepressants in America it was first
opiates yeah then it was like cocaine
then it was barbiturates absolutely for
is a big cocaine guy they would inject
it and I mean to be fair if you
didn't actually like know about it you
know what I mean like no I don't think
if I didn't know about and I took it I
was not not for me no but like I think
people didn't know how to associate like
feeling good with being good
because there was much less things like
right in the modern world we're
constantly exposed to like candy bars
and yeah all right so everyone kind
of knows yeah well this tastes good but
it's not good for this feels good but
it's not good for how to join common
yeah you got it give me a job yeah yeah
I I think I will say that's fair if you
can't figure out how to apply that's
kind of the first test definite that's a
sad realization though yeah I think a
big part of the culture and working with
you is that you have to absolutely all
the all the information is available you
have to find it yeah and that's the
world today everything's available I
know I'm just like who asks yeah yeah
what is the next thing for the music
industry actor oh well we okay we were
debating on the music you want to defend
your position on the music industry is
weak now not I'm not standing that
nothing you've changed my mind
I haven't changed your mind okay yeah I
mean I think that the music industry's
actually one of the most healthy
industries I think that music today is
incredible
I think that it's well there's search
engines social media I mean I think I
think what airplane manufacturing does
it unhealthy industry right I think
there's tons
but no I think that the music industry
because the production
I mean you genuinely have like lots of
little peep like people in the world
dear viewers things that we should just
let all these big companies go bankrupt
oh yeah yeah well we started with okay
you know we're bringing back the French
Revolution we're bringing the guillotine
back whose heads were chopping off right
and like you know it's the Congress and
the large companies right yeah but then
we realize that you know we do live in a
democracy and we can just solve this
problem who's voting for Nancy Pelosi
and who's voting for Mitch McConnell yes
I'm voting for these people bye-bye
bye-bye
thank you for serving us terribly for 25
years yeah so I mean the big companies
are the same way right
does our economy does our whole middle
class exist a prop up these these
companies that are you know strip mining
themselves to stock buybacks right so we
got to let all these companies fail
we'll make the planes someone's gonna
make the planes gonna make the plane and
right you know guess what with the death
of Boeing there's gonna be a lot more
interest in what's wrong with stock
buybacks what stock buybacks give
executives a way to get their money out
while basically like it's it's it's
they're not aligned with the company
it's them versus the company and like
dividends on the other hand are their
people little dividends the stock
buybacks are just the same thing you can
do the math out there the same well my
favorite finance explained it to me and
he from a very technical perspective
they are
from a very technical perspective it's
just letting all the people buy out
basically like it's reinvesting your
dividend for you sure if everybody who
wasn't part of the buyback just
reinvested their dividend it would be
the same thing at stock buybacks
but the problem is dividends come to you
whether you like it or not
buybacks reward an investor that's
paying hyper attention and that is never
your middle class person with a 401 K
they never benefit from stock bonds and
it also encourages this whole the CEO of
Boeing doesn't give a about Boeing
right
these people aren't founders these
companies the founders died years and
years and years ago right it's time for
these companies these companies have
gone through the whole business cycle
and it's time to let them die ha ha yes
yes we must make the number go up
ok everybody try the number chant any
Boeing is too big to fail no it's not
let's let it fail oh no it failed Oh No
look at the time we shut down the whole
economy because you know a bunch of
people freaked out and you're telling me
Boeing's too big to fail yeah like when
the Dow gets hacked sure when the Dow
gets hacked sure aetherium can revert
their whole blockchain but when a
theorem gets act
if they were too big to fail why
couldn't they build reliable new planes
yeah very they've already failed do I
think Trump has stocks on hydro chloric
win alone he's this this whole thing
battles but like Trump cares about like
a couple of million dollars that he
makes on some stupid stock thing yeah I
my read on what Trump cares about is
Trump cares about one thing
do the people love Trump do the people
love Trump oh I'm gonna have a big rally
and they're all gonna cheer when I say
Trump what's up with the f was the app
for the Trump or for the for the for the
companies or for the stream
are you still planning on making an AR
head set back today it may not be the AR
headsets
today it could be in the future what do
you mean like uh on making the AR head
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah no I mean you
know I was just exploring I was
exploring talking about medicines
recommendation guys if you're drinking
fish tank cleaner you have much deeper
problems it was some guy said on Twitter
no actually I think we can talk about
that no don't normal people talking
about medicine I not only think it's
important I think that a lot of these a
lot of these expert organizations are
not better than a intelligent individual
reading the interent
I think if an individual knows how to
read the internet knows how to put
information together they can outperform
like come on the World Health
Organization all there's no human they
told you that that masks don't help you
and then some new study came out two
weeks later that's a nasty Wow maybe it
had to do with the fact that we were out
of masks and I think lying are people is
a good idea yo just if otherwise why
would doctors ever wear masks masks and
do anything no but we have to stop the
bailouts for absolutely everything
starting with the college education
well I mean this is a huge problem if
you trust me all of the all of the you
know interpretive feminist dance majors
would dry up real fast if the government
wasn't covering their student loans
turns out the world just too many
interpretive feminist answers absolutely
but they can pay for it out of pocket
this is a free country well no to be
fair though if you're a bank who do you
want to invest in them or a petroleum
engineer you know maybe not right now in
the petroleum engineer but that's the
top pay stopping major yeah petroleum
engineer where can we find the oil I
just you always see there on the top of
that they want us to test
that's what they're asking stocks
finally made it to a gorge tomb when's
the wedding and will you invite twitch
chat now off weddings are illegal
haven't you heard of Cologne a virus
they apparently canceled Burning Man up
by the way I think this is gonna be the
best year of Burning Man ever who wants
to go to the playa we're hosting our own
Burning Man AR has hella potential yes
we agree with that are we going to the
clubhouse
should we show them the beach yo man
look at all that social distancing out
there on the ocean oh you want to stop
at this thingy oh the Cliff House where
their petroleum engineering is in Texas
[Music]
[Laughter]
there's a long way from the phone to
fall show them what's the value of
college or some do you wants to be a
programmer no you can't go outside bro
I just did what are you gonna do about
it
right next to you George I don't believe
they're here if someone actually came up
to us would be funny I won't shake your
hand no those are illegal in the era of
coronavirus take us into the water oh
the time we walked by the cliffs and
went in the water sure I was gonna die I
was sure I was gonna die
College helps you get a job and forces
her to study yeah PG stream' please yeah
that's why it was that's why we flipped
the camera around
let's call the cops chat do it do it
behind you in blue t-shirt is there a
guy behind me in a blue t-shirt that's
right good point
Jones already above you yeah I wish
someone was working someone's on the
drone please you know what a drone ad if
someone gets a drone over here I'll
attach a hundred dollars I'm just gonna
say the same thing alright what are
their predictions do we have before we
go
they are Mars AI Tech's about to get
really do it
I think BIOS still kind of not gonna
happen because I tried to fold a simple
ass protein and it's too hot
Oh what personal flying things happen
now what is your keyboard keyboard I
don't have keyboard what about China Oh
in 2021 yay applause follow me you know
the Japanese will make that happen
predict when do you think they're gonna
open the economy oh pretty eclectic
we're gonna open the economy so shorts
on I'll give you my shirt prediction
right then I think at the end of April
most things are gonna open with a few
crazy states don't oh I'm gonna look
into nandi I'm definitely looking to nab
do on the next stream guys installing
CUDA such a pain cuz Nvidia hates you
bro why was i living in China China
do I think the US and China will go to
war within the next 20 years
no it doesn't make sense for anybody
what's the war gonna be open the u.s.
channel every minute I'm the US and
Russia went to war
oh yeah it didn't happen
why can't biotech work I agree why do
you think I took second that's one of my
four versions at the singularity well
yeah the singularity is not gonna happen
till the 23rd when we'll discuss the
cyber war is happening right now this is
only ten-year predictions
yeah the cyber war just sucks cuz you
don't hear about it well Microsoft throw
me no absolutely not
this is the end the shutdown no good way
no way they and the governor's notice to
the minute they close the shutdown sorry
bro that's the most powerful you were
ever gonna be in your life predictions
for Tesla making out of it they're not
gonna ever make a singularity in 2030
end of the 23rd is the singularity but
the 2010 the 2020s is going to be a
great decade what do you mean by drone
warfare well some cop chase a guy down
with a drone yes oh yeah singularity is
not happening we're never going to Mars
either like an individual no guys
hacking is like kind of not real they
think the competitive solitaire scene
will hit this year making
looks like look you guys I I did feel
bad for Libra I do oh yeah next what
about a neural link and decent ink a lot
of the neuro-link stuff is overhyped
about what it can do but I do think by
the end of the 2020s we're gonna have
something great I definitely people
think that it's gonna be like magical
it's gonna be yeah if you if you're
paralyzed or like a quadriplegic the
next day the next time the next 10 years
if you actually are like locked in your
body are gonna be amazing
again it's really it's gonna be even is
gonna get people who just like you know
love him more than anything else talk
about a product with engagement you know
if someone's like locked in their body
and can't use a keyboard in the house
I'm not sure that things like neuro-link
are gonna outperform I don't think
things like neural link will outperform
a keyboard and mouse and touch screen
well no one is out five will trying to
dominate with AI George's girlfriend's
bad hey thanks bro yeah she does joke
shall leave me I mean I think she'll
leave me too you know what I mean
alright guys I think that's us man it's
time thank you all for joining us
predictions a are more self-driving cars
gonna happen a lot more is gonna happen
the 2020s are going to be a great decade
it is a wonderful time to be alive
everybody go outside unless you're old
or immunocompromised then you might want
to stay inside but otherwise stay safe
always they say if we love safety safety
is one of our key values on this stream
you